{
  "level": 4,
  "unit": 2,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "Will you ___________ the drain?", "answer": "unblock" },
        { "prompt": "An ___________ kangaroo is small.", "answer": "unborn" },
        { "prompt": "___________ the gate to go in.", "answer": "Unchain" },
        { "prompt": "I will ___________ the dishwasher.", "answer": "unload" },
        { "prompt": "We ___________ the door to go in.", "answer": "unlock" },
        {
          "prompt": "There was a ___________ on dog food.",
          "answer": "recall"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I have to ___________ all the math.",
          "answer": "relearn"
        },
        { "prompt": "___________ your used books.", "answer": "resell" },
        { "prompt": "We had to ___________ the clothes.", "answer": "rewash" },
        {
          "prompt": "Please ___________ the ball of yarn.",
          "answer": "rewind"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The artist's painting was ___________ .",
          "answer": "imperfect"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We had to go the ___________ way to avoid the traffic accident.",
          "answer": "indirect"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The math answer was ___________ .",
          "answer": "incorrect"
        },
        { "prompt": "Breaking the law is ___________ .", "answer": "illegal" },
        {
          "prompt": "That movie star tends to ___________ .",
          "answer": "overact"
        },
        { "prompt": "Don’t ___________ the coffee.", "answer": "overheat" },
        { "prompt": "We took the ___________ downtown.", "answer": "subway" },
        {
          "prompt": "We had to ___________ the ingredients.",
          "answer": "premix"
        },
        { "prompt": "Let’s ___________ where to meet.", "answer": "preplan" },
        { "prompt": "We did not ___________ the meal.", "answer": "supersize" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I have ___________ shirts at home.", "answer": "thrity" },
        {
          "prompt": "We walked the ___________ of the bridge.",
          "answer": "width"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ towns are very cold.",
          "answer": "northern"
        },
        { "prompt": "My sister is in ___________ grade.", "answer": "fifth" },
        { "prompt": "Which hat should I ___________ ?", "answer": "choose" },
        { "prompt": "Do not ___________ the hot pan!", "answer": "touch" },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ made a special dessert.",
          "answer": "chef"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She has a ___________ to win the prize.",
          "answer": "chance"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ struck out everyone.",
          "answer": "pitcher"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ smells of baked bread.",
          "answer": "kitchen"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I ___________ a picture of my house.",
          "answer": "sketched"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I like ___________ on my hamburger.",
          "answer": "ketchup"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Will the lion ___________ the food away?",
          "answer": "snatch"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ relaxes your muscles.",
          "answer": "stretching"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "We need to ___________ to the hospital.",
          "answer": "rush"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "He began to ___________ about his chores.",
          "answer": "whine"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The classroom is a ___________ of activity.",
          "answer": "whirl"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "___________ the king his royal crown.",
          "answer": "bring"
        },
        { "prompt": "We made a bar ___________ in class.", "answer": "graph" },
        {
          "prompt": "That is an old ___________ of our town.",
          "answer": "photo"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "Can you ___________ this paper?", "answer": "shred" },
        {
          "prompt": "Did you hear her ___________ with joy?",
          "answer": "shriek"
        },
        { "prompt": "We ate ___________ for dinner.", "answer": "shrimp" },
        {
          "prompt": "We can ___________ the large picture.",
          "answer": "shrink"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I read the ___________ for the play.",
          "answer": "script"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A ___________ will hold the picture up.",
          "answer": "screw"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The car might ___________ to a halt.",
          "answer": "screech"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Try to ___________ up this mess.",
          "answer": "straighten"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Use the ___________ to carry the backpack.",
          "answer": "straps"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "In class, we studied a ___________ of hair.",
          "answer": "strand"
        },
        { "prompt": "Seeds ___________ in the spring.", "answer": "sprout" },
        {
          "prompt": "I like to ___________ out on the couch.",
          "answer": "sprawl"
        },
        { "prompt": "I ___________ out of bed.", "answer": "sprang" },
        { "prompt": "We were ___________ in the pool.", "answer": "splashing" },
        {
          "prompt": "The broken pen left a ___________ of ink.",
          "answer": "splotch"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It was a ___________ to win the game.",
          "answer": "thrill"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I felt a ___________ of pain in my head.",
          "answer": "throb"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I ate ice cream for my sore ___________ .",
          "answer": "throat"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Practice ___________ by finding the lowest price before buying something.",
          "answer": "thrift"
        },
        { "prompt": "Go ___________ that first door.", "answer": "through" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "He threw a ___________ at the board.", "answer": "dart" },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ let us enter the gate.",
          "answer": "guard"
        },
        { "prompt": "He won the attendance ___________ .", "answer": "award" },
        {
          "prompt": "Are the animals in the ___________ ?",
          "answer": "backyard"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I don’t like to ___________ with you.",
          "answer": "argue"
        },
        { "prompt": "The fire threw off a ___________ .", "answer": "spark" },
        { "prompt": "Her arrow hit the ___________ .", "answer": "target" },
        {
          "prompt": "It was ___________ to bring a sweater.",
          "answer": "smart"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "A battery has an electric ___________ .",
          "answer": "charge"
        },
        { "prompt": "The ___________ we bought is soft.", "answer": "carpet" },
        { "prompt": "Water made the wood ___________ .", "answer": "warp" },
        { "prompt": "Shut the ___________ when you leave.", "answer": "door" },
        { "prompt": "We passed by an old ___________ .", "answer": "fort" },
        { "prompt": "I work best in the ___________ .", "answer": "morning" },
        { "prompt": "The ___________ had pretty feathers.", "answer": "stork" },
        { "prompt": "The telephone ___________ is broken.", "answer": "cord" },
        { "prompt": "I was ___________ out after the game.", "answer": "worn" },
        {
          "prompt": "If it is ___________ outside, we stay in.",
          "answer": "stormy"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Is the ___________ of the apple edible?",
          "answer": "core"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Please don’t ___________ me with that story again.",
          "answer": "bore"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "The ___________ boy missed school.", "answer": "sickly" },
        {
          "prompt": "There were ___________ any pears left.",
          "answer": "hardly"
        },
        { "prompt": "Let’s run ___________ to the bus.", "answer": "quickly" },
        { "prompt": "Walk ___________ on the ice.", "answer": "slowly" },
        {
          "prompt": "He wrapped his foot ___________ .",
          "answer": "carefully"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The parade is a ___________ event.",
          "answer": "wonderful"
        },
        { "prompt": "The poem was ___________ .", "answer": "beautiful" },
        {
          "prompt": "The athlete was very ___________ .",
          "answer": "graceful"
        },
        { "prompt": "A ___________ of honey is sweet.", "answer": "spoonful" },
        {
          "prompt": "The ___________ hid him from view.",
          "answer": "darkness"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The empty bag looked ___________ .",
          "answer": "shapeless"
        },
        { "prompt": "The actress looked ___________ .", "answer": "ageless" },
        {
          "prompt": "An ___________ can last a long time.",
          "answer": "illness"
        },
        { "prompt": "His ___________ knew no bounds.", "answer": "goodness" },
        { "prompt": "The ___________ couch was new.", "answer": "spotless" },
        { "prompt": "The haircut was ___________ .", "answer": "painless" },
        {
          "prompt": "Video games were her ___________ .",
          "answer": "weakness"
        },
        { "prompt": "The ___________ blue looks black.", "answer": "darkest" },
        { "prompt": "The sky was ___________ at dusk.", "answer": "clearest" },
        {
          "prompt": "He thanked his ___________ mother.",
          "answer": "thoughtful"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
